viewpure.com 2018-11-23

# ViewPure Terms of Service | Privacy Policy |

## Terms Of Service

Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern ViewPure.com's relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.

The term 'ViewPure.com' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is ViewPure.com. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * From time to time, this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of United States.

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how ViewPure.com uses and protects any information that you give ViewPure.com when you use this website.

ViewPure.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ViewPure.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

 **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

See here for [Full Cookie Policy and for Cookie Consent](http://www.viewpure.com/pages/cookie-policy)

 **Links to other 3rd party websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at ViewPure.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to ViewPure.com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Viewpure does not share personal information with third parties nor does it store any information about user visits to this site other than to analyze and optimize user browsing experience through the use of cookies. Users may turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing their specific browser settings. Viewpure makes use of the application programming interface (API) made available by YouTube.com. Please note that Viewpure and any of its owners have no control over the videos made available on this website. If users do not want their YouTube videos to appear on other websites including Viewpure, consider disabling the embedding option of their videos from their personal YouTube account.  

 **Third-party Advertisers**

Viewpure has contracted with 3rd party ad networks to serve advertisements. These third-party ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on this website. The use of technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) are sometimes used to personalize the advertising messages.

Viewpure does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

The Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)'s [opt-out location for personally identifiable ads is located here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad networks (see ads.txt) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Viewpure's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Data Security**

Viewpure uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Viewpure and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Viewpure ** ** makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

 **Childrens' Privacy**  

Viewpure does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access Viewpure at any time or in any manner. If Viewpure learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on Viewpure without verified parental consent, then Viewpure will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

 **International Website Vistors**

Viewpure is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing Viewpure from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Viewpure website, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

## Copyright Infringement and DMCA Policy

Viewpure respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that material located on or linked to by Viewpure violates your copyright, you are encouraged to notify Viewpure using the "Contact us page". Viewpure will respond to all such notices, including as required or appropriate by removing the infringing material or disabling all links to the infringing material. Note that Viewpure does not specifically control the video view pages of this site. YouTube has direct control of the videos played on this site. If the DMCA material is on the video view page, please see YouTube to assist you.

## Disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by ViewPure.com and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of ViewPure.com. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, ViewPure.com takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

Viewpure is in no way associated with YouTube.com. Viewpure, its owners and affliates, do not own, store, keep, or modify any of the videos available on this website. All the videos displayed on this website are copyrighted by their respective owners. Viewpure cannot prevent videos from being displayed on this website.  

## Indemnification

You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Viewpure, its contractors, and its licensors, and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising out of your use of the Website, including but not limited to your violation of this Agreement.

This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between Viewpure and you concerning the subject matter hereof, and they may only be modified by a written amendment signed by an authorized executive of Viewpure, or by the posting by Viewpure of a revised version. The prevailing party in any action or proceeding to enforce this Agreement shall be entitled to costs and attorneys’ fees. If any part of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable, that part will be construed to reflect the parties’ original intent, and the remaining portions will remain in full force and effect. A waiver by either party of any term or condition of this Agreement or any breach thereof, in any one instance, will not waive such term or condition or any subsequent breach thereof. You may assign your rights under this Agreement to any party that consents to, and agrees to be bound by, its terms and conditions; Viewpure may assign its rights under this Agreement without condition. This Agreement will be binding upon and will inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assigns.
